<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<program_description xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="../../docs/w3-ws/specificationData/description.xsd">
       <program provider="PyXMCDA"
              name="GammaP"
              displayName="GammaP"
              version="1.0" />
       <documentation>
              <description>This web service allows to compute clusters of alternatives from an outranking relation with the aim of maximizing the indifference between the alternatives inside the same cluster, and minimizing the indifference between different clusters.</description>
              <contact>Alexandru Olteanu (alexandru.olteanu@uni.lu)</contact>
       </documentation>
       
       
       <parameters>
              
              <input id="alternatives" name="alternatives" displayName="alternatives"
                     isoptional="0">
                     
                     <documentation>
                            <description>A list of alternatives. Alternatives can be activated or dezactivated via the &lt;active&gt; tag (true or false). By default (no &lt;active&gt; tag), alternatives are considered as active. </description>
                     </documentation>
                     <xmcda tag="alternatives">
                     </xmcda>
              </input>
              
              <input id="relation"
                     name="relation"
                     displayName="outranking relation"
                     isoptional="0">
                     
                     <documentation>
                            <description>The outranking relation used to compare the objects.</description>
                     </documentation>
                     <xmcda tag="alternativesComparisons"/>
              </input>
              
              <input id="parameters"
                     name="parameters"
                     displayName="parameters"
                     isoptional="0">
                     <documentation>
                            <description>The 4 method parameters: min (real value) - the minimum of the valuation domain of the relation; max (real value) - the maximum of the valuation domain of the relation; cut (real value) - the cut level of the relation (for a relation valued between 0(false) and 1(true) we normally have a 0.5 cut level; for a relation valued between -1 and 1 we normally have a 0 cut level); bipolar (boolean value) - the type of cut on the relation (false means a classic cut where every value above or equal to the cut level is considered as 'true', everything below the cut level is considered 'false'; true means a bipolar cut, where any value above or equal to the cut level is considered 'true', every value below ... if you read all the way here than contact me.</description>
                     </documentation>
                     <xmcda tag="methodParameters"/>
              </input>
              
              <output id="messages"
                     name="messages"
                     displayName="messages">
                     <documentation>
                            <description>A list of messages generated by the algorithm.</description>
                     </documentation>
                     <xmcda tag="methodMessages"/>
              </output>
              
              <output id="output"
                     name="output"
                     displayName="output">
                     <documentation>
                            <description>The alternatives clusters affectations.</description>
                     </documentation>
                     <xmcda tag="alternativesAffectations"/>
              </output>
              
       </parameters>
</program_description>
